*Naruto Shippuden OP1 Playing*
♪ This is about to be so cringy. ♪
*Weeb cover of Naruto Shippuden OP1*
ARE YOU READY!?
To start Naruto Shippuden off
Naruto returns to the hidden leaf village
after training with Jiraiya for two and a half years.
He later gets reacquainted with
Uselessness and Kakashi and undergoes the Bell Test,
and as a result Naruto and Uselessness successfully
pass the Bell Test, and acquire both bells.
Meanwhile in the Hidden Sand Village
Gaara is captured by an Akatsuki member named Deidara.
With that said, Kankuro goes after
Deidara to retrieve Gaara.
Sit your weak ass down.
After some time Kankuro catches up to Deidara,
and is forced to go up against his partner Sasori.
Sasori then poisons that bitch,
and then leaves him there to die.
A little after Hidden Sand Shinobi recovers Kankuro
and brings him to an infirmary.
At this point in time the Hidden Leaf Village
is notified by the situation
and dispatches Naruto, Kakashi, Uselessness,
Temari, and Team Guy to rescue Gaara.
But time is ticking because Gaara
is getting extracted from his Tailed Beast.
On the arrival at the hidden sand,
Naruto's squad visits Kankuro's infirmary room
where this random old bitch attacks them.
This old bitch is later identified as Chiyo.
While in the infirmary Uselessness creates
antidotes for Sasori's poison.
Also curing Kankuro from the effects of it.
So moving forward Naruto's squad heads out,
leaving Temari in the Hidden Sand
and bringing Chiyo along.
As both Team Guy and Naruto's squad
arrive at the Akatsuki hideout,
Gaara dies from his Tailed Beast being extracted.
Gaara: How you gonna kill me off in the first season.
They then breach the hideout,
and there's Deidara and Sasori.
Deidara takes Gaara and then flies away,
beating Naruto and Kakashi out of the hideout.
This left Uselessness and Chiyo to handle Sasori.
*Pokémon battle music playing*
(Rest in peace)
Moving forward Naruto and Kakashi
manages to recover Gaara.
Deidara attempts to escape but then gets cornered
until he self destructs.
As a response Kakashi uses his mangekyou sharingan
to absorb the explosion, ultimately saving everyone.
With granny Chiyo having nothing to live for
because she already has one fucking foot in the grave,
she then uses the reanimation jutsu
sacrificing her life to save Gaara.
(Rest in peace)
After all that everyone returned to their village,
and lived happily ever after.
For now.
And oh yeah, Deidara is still alive
and gets a new partner named Tobi.
*Weeb cover of Naruto Shippuden OP2*
Moving forward, Naruto is assigned a mission
with Uselesness, Yamato, and Sai.
Yamato is the substitute leader for Team Kakashi,
and Sai's just there to paint fucking animals.
They're assigned to go to Tenchi bridge
to capture Sasori's spy.
On their arrival Yamato approaches the bridge
disguised as Hiruko, or Sasori's fucking puppet.
Shortly after, Orochimaru appears and
Kabuto karate chops the fuck out of Yamato.
With that said, Naruto, Uselessness,
and Sai assemble on the bridge.
Orochimaru then provokes Naruto
pushing him to enter the kyuubi cloak form.
(Sakura gets rekt)
As a resolution to stop Naruto's rampage,
Yamato uses the Hokage Style: Elder Jutsu
Tenth Edict on Enlightment.
While that's happening, Sai groups up with
Orochimaru and Kabuto and heads to their hideout.
Using a clone, Yamato traces them down to the hideout
and given the clone's assistance,
Naruto, Uselessness, and Yamato enter.
Soon after they find Sai, and search
room to room for Sasuke.
Sai finds Sasuke and attempts to capture him.
(door creaks open)
Sasuke: Think it's funny waking me from my wet dream.
Sai: *gasps*
(Sai's snakes hissing)
*KA-BOOM*
Naruto, Uselessness, and Yamato
then rushes to Sasuke's location.
After a nice little reunion, Sasuke obliterates
all of them, and retreats with Orochimaru and Kabuto.
Returning to the Hidden Leaf, Naruto undergoes
intense training for chakra nature and chakra form
with the intention of creating a new jutsu.
At this time two Akatsuki members
Hidan and Kakuzu are invading the Land of Fire,
killing innocent Shinobi.
As a result, Team Asuma and a couple
another Shinobi are dispatched.
Attempting to kill Hidan, Asuma dies.
Rest in peace!
Soon after reinforcements come, a bit fucking late,
and both Hidan and Kakuzu retreat.
Shikamaru then seeks vengeance and
goes after them once again with Ino, Choji, and Kakashi.
They manage to ambush Hidan and Kakuzu,
and so Shikamaru uses his shadow possession jutsu
on Hidan and leaves him here, where he can fuck his shit up.
Moments after, Naruto arrives at the battlefield and is like
"hey, I'm about to fuck your spaghetti ass up",
and uses his new jutsu wind style rasen shuriken
to defeat Kakuzu.
Rest in peace!
And at this current moment, Shikamaru successfully
traps Hidan blowing his body up to a fuck ton of pieces
leaving him a hole to die.
Rest in peace!
Moving forward Orochimaru is in a weakened state
and needs a new vessel.
Sasuke takes advantage of this and kills Orochimaru.
Sasuke then gathers three members for the Hebi.
Karin, Jugo, and Suigetsu.
While searching for Itachi, Sasuke's ambushed by Deidara.
Sasuke then fucks his shit up,
causing Deidara to self destruct as a last resort.
Rest in peace!
This causes a massive explosion in which
Sasuke manages to escape.
At this current point, the Hidden Leaf dispatches
Team Kakashi and Team Kurenai to capture Sasuke.
While searching for Sasuke, Naruto finds himself
bumping into Itachi where he receives a gift from him.
Moving forward, while this whole search for Sasuke
thing is going on, Jiraiya leaves the Hidden Leaf Village
to investigate the Hidden Rain
for information on the Akatsuki.
While on this mission Jiraiya had to fight
his former student Konan and a little after
he had to fight Pain.
Both members of the Akatsuki.
And as a result, Jiraiya dies.
Rest in peace!
But right on the brink of death,
Jiraiya sends intel on Pain to the Hidden Leaf.
So our boy Jiraiya didn't die for no reason.
Moving forward, Sasuke gets the location where
he can find Itachi through one of Itachi's clones.
So Sasuke goes to the location he was told,
and on his way he crosses paths with Kisame.
Kisame allows Sasuke through but prevents
Jugo, Karin, and Suigetsu to follow.
As Sasuke enters the Uchiha hideout,
there he sees his brother Itachi.
They then fight and Sasuke ends up using his strongest jutsu
(lightning and dramatic music)
Sasuke: I call this jutsu Kirin,
now be gone with the booty clap BITCH.
(lightning)
(roars)
Itachi: Did he just say boo—?
So then Itachi then gets back up using his susanoo,
and through desperation Sasuke tries to force chakra,
resulting in the curse mark unleashing this monstrosity.
Orichamaru then plays peek-a-boo
and Itachi smacks that bitch with the totsuka blade.
Feeling that curse mark away,
shortly after Itachi collapses as well as Sasuke.
Oh yeah Itachi died by the way.
Rest in peace!
Tobi then captures Sasuke and tells him the truth of Itachi,
which is that Itachi was just trying to
protect Sasuke in the Hidden Leaf Village.
After hearing this Sasuke unlocks his mangekyou sharingan
and sets the goal to destroy the Hidden Leaf Village.
Sasuke then joins the Akatsuki
in which he's then assigned to capture the
atl Jinchuuriki killer bee.
He successfully defeats and captures killer bee,
but later on it's revealed that he captured a clone.
Moving forward, Naruto returns to the Hidden Leaf
and now gets the news about Jiraiya.
He falls into a depression, but then eventually
overcomes it, and then undergoes training
for senjutsu at Mount Myoboku.
While Naruto is training at Mount Myoboku,
the Hidden Leaf is attacked by Pain
and eventually annihilated.
Naruto then appears after mastering senjutsu,
and takes on all of the six Pains at once.
Like the DISGUSTING beast he is.
After destroying five of the six Pains,
Naruto is then pinned.
Hinata then comes to the rescue but, yeah.
After witnessing this, Naruto only sees
his kyuubi cloak form, reaching a whole six tails.
Through desperation, Naruto attempts to release nine tails,
but is then stopped by his father Minato.
Minato then suppresses the kyuubi chakra,
leaving Naruto to do one thing.
SMACK THAT BITCH WITH A RASENGAN
Upon defeating Pain, Naruto utilizes sage mode
and one of Pain's black rods to track
the individual who is controlling Pain.
Naruto locates the person and discovers that it was
one of Jiraiya's former students, Nagato.
Given the situation, Naruto then gives
one of his POWERFUL speeches, which brings Nagato to believe
Naruto has the power to bring peace to the Shinobi world.
Nagato then uses Rinne Rebirth,
reviving everyone who died in the Pain asssault.
Oh yeah, Nagato dies in the process.
Rest in peace!
*Weeb cover of Naruto Shippuden OP8*
Moving forward, Naruto returns to the
Hidden Leaf Village as a hero,
and due to the fact Tsunade was placed
under a coma from the Pain assault,
Danzo was assigned hokage, best hokage right here boys.
With that said, Sasuke sees the five hokage summit
as an opportunity to kill Danzo.
Taking on four hokages, Sasuke pushes
his way to get to Danzo.
But mid battle, the fighting is then disrupted by Tobi.
Tobi then declares the fourth great ninja war,
explaining his ultimate goal, Project Tsuki No Me.
Naruto: Uh Sakura, what was that?
What did you just say?
Sakura: What I said was, I love you Naruto.
(Get the fuck outta here with yo lying ass)
Tobi then transports Sasuke to Danzo,
leaving Danzo no other choice but to fight.
Placed in a predicament, Danzo then takes Karin hostage
and with Sasuke being Sasuke...
Karin: Sasuke help! Do something!
Sasuke: No worries, I got you.
(lightning beams)
As a last resort Danzo uses his
Reverse Tetragram Sealing Jutsu,
self destructing, and... killing no one.
(laughter)
Rest in peace!
Uselessness then shows up trying to kill Sasuke,
but nearly dies if it wasn't for Kakashi.
Kakashi and Sasuke then fight,
and Uselessness goes in for the round two,
but this bitch nearly dies again
if it wasn't for Naruto.
So after that, Naruto and Sasuke then have a brief talk,
and shortly after that Sasuke and Tobi retreat.
With Sasuke's eyes being all fucked up from
overusing the sharingan, he then decides to get
Itachi's eyes implanted, enabling him to
acquire the Enternal Mangekyou Sharingan.
Moving forward, Tsunade wakes from her coma,
and is reassigned Hokage.
With that said, Naruto is then assigned to go to
Turtle Island along with Killer Bee
to prevent them from getting captured
and extracted from the Tailed Beast.
Yamato and Guy also come along,
and Naruto is not aware of the plan
and is told that this is a S rank mission.
On Turtle Island, Naruto fights the nine tails within him,
attempting to conquer is kyuubi chakra.
With the help of his mother Kushina,
Naruto defeats the nine tails, and acquires kyuubi mode.
And shortly after, Kisame appears from the Samahada
that Killer Bee has been carrying around.
Attempting to escape, Kisame is intercepted by Guy.
At the brink of being extracted for information,
Kisame summons water strikes to consume him,
preventing any information from getting leaked.
Also, at the mist of dove, Kisame uses a
water strike summoning to send intel on the
Jinjuuriki's location to Kabuto and Tobi,
who are now acquaintances, and oh yeah.
Rest in peace!
Moving forward, Tobi is looking Nagato's corpse
so he can acquire the rinnegan.
He then goes to Konan asking her where she put the body
but she refuses, and attempts to kill him.
Tobi was not having it and defeats Konan
placing her under a genjutsu forcing her to
reveal the location of Nagato's body.
Successfully finding the body,
Tobi steals the rinnegan for himself,
and oh yeah Konan's dead.
Rest in peace!
Moving forward, Kabuto masters the reanimation jutsu.
Using it, Kabuto reanimates Deidara
and heads to Turtle Island.
Capturing Yamato and using him
to power up an army of white zetsus.
With no time to waste, Kabuto releases the
army of white zetsus as well as reanimated Shinobi.
And all five great nations form an alliance
creating the allied shinobi forces.
With all that said and done,
the fourth great ninja war begins.
At this current point in time,
Naruto starts getting suspicious
because he's being confined on Turtle Island.
He then barges through the guards
and senses the war using sage mode.
Both Naruto and Killer Bee then escapes Turtle Island,
and heads to the battlefield, but are then intercepted
by the Raikage and Tsunade.
They manage to get through the two,
but now face another challenge,
which is to defeat Itachi and Nagato who were reanimated.
Using the gift that Itachi gave to Naruto while back,
Itachi regains control over his own body,
undoing the edo tensei.
Itachi then steals Nagato using totsuka blade
and heads to Kabuto to stop the edo tensei.
Moving forward, Madara is reanimated
and makes his appearance on the battlefield.
Pretty much spreading everyone's cheeks
and even dropping a fucking meteor on them.
Fighting together to stop Madara,
the five hokage struggle to keep up with his power.
Meanwhile, while that's going on,
Naruto and Killer Bee are fighting the reanimated Jinchuuriki
(Oh shit where are the tissues I'm having a nose bleed.)
The Jinchuuriki then go into their Tailed Beast mode,
and as a result of the situation,
Naruto befriends Kurama obtaining bijuu mode.
Moving forward, Sasuke recovers from his eye implants
and heads to the Hidden Leaf.
On his way there, Sasuke sees Itachi
and follows him all the way to Kabuto's hideout.
They then team up and defeat Kabuto using izanami.
Using genjutsu, Itachi commands Kabuto to do the
hand signs to release the edo tensei.
With that said, Itachi says his farewell to Sasuke.
The only person who remained from the edo tensei
is Madara, because if you really think about it,
he's fucking Madara.
Moments after releasing the edo tensei,
Jugo and Suigetsu arrive.
Sasuke then uses Jugo's sage chakra,
and Anko's curse mark to resurrect Orichimaru.
Moving forward, Naruto is now going up against Tobi.
Using a rasegan, Naruto bashes that mask
revealing Tobi's true identity.
Apparently he's Obito Uchiha,
one of Kakashi's childhood comrads,
or the guy who lost his shit after seeing
(loud fighting strike)
Shortly after Madara appears after
demolishing the five hokage, as expected,
and works side by side with Obito
successfully summoning the ten tails.
*thud*
Rest in peace!
Moving forward, with the help of Orochimaru,
the former hokage reanimated,
Sasuke decides to protect the Hidden Leaf
and heads to the battlefield along with the former hokage.
Team 7 is now reunited and Obito and Kakashi are
in the Kamui's dimension settling their EPIC battle.
After losing the fight, Obito teleports
back to the battlefield then merges with the ten tails
becoming the ten tails Jinchuuriki.
Obito then uses the ten tails to spawn the divine tree,
and moments after he's defeated by Naruto and Sasuke
and extracted from his tailed beast.
Upon defeating Obito, Naruto then gives one of his
POWERFUL speeches transforming Obito
into a good guy as corny as that sounds.
As a result, Obito attempts to use the rinne rebirth
to revive the casualties of the war,
but is then soon after stopped by a black zetsu.
Under black zetsu's control, the rinne rebirth
is then used to Madara.
Madara is then given a rinnegan by white zetsu,
and uses it to summon the Gedo Statue,
and absorbs every tailed beast.
Upon completion he then merges with the Gedo Statue,
becoming the ten tailed Jinjuuriki.
Oh yeah and I forgot to mention,
(heartbeat)
Rest in peace!
(metal blade slashing)
Oh wait, this isn't Akame ga Kill
They actually end up surviving,
and on top of that, they end up getting
a power buff by the Sage of Six Paths.
*Weeb cover of Naruto Shippuden OP16*
Guy in the background: Yo the fuck you doing.
Moe: I was just over here singing, yo yo CHILL
PUT AWAY THE BELT!
(slapping noises)
Guy in the background: Don't you ever sing at night.
Moving forward, Guy's looking like a burnt marshmallow
after using the eight gates against Madara.
Madara then goes out to Kakashi for his sharingan
and uses it to travel to the Kimui's dimension.
There he steals Obito's rinnegan
because this bitch couldn't destroy it.
Always fucking shit up.
Now that he's acquired this,
Madara now has all the requirements for Project Tsuki No Me,
and executes the infinite Tsuki No Me.
Thank you Uselessness, now everyone
is sleep cause yo bitch ass.
And now the only people who remain
to stop the infinate Tsuki No Me is the OG Team 7.
But little did we know Black Zetsu backstabs Madara.
Get it, cause Black Zetsu stabbed
his arm through Madara's back.
(Get yo ugly ass out of here.)
Black Zetsu then absorbs Madara,
and the chakra from the divine tree to resurrect Kaguya.
AKA the mother of all chakra.
Apparently this was Black Zetsu's plan
from the very beginning, so Team 7
fights the final boss and successfully defeats
and seals away Kaguya, and oh yeah,
Obito dies in the process.
Rest in peace!
All that's left is for Naruto and Sasuke
to undo the infinite Tsuki No Me.
By simultaneously doing the rat hand sign,
but Sasuke is then all like nah bitch.
What the Shinobi world needs is REVOLUTION.
With that said, both Naruto and Sasuke
head to the final valley to settle their final battle.
They then end their battle with their
signature rasengan and chidori clash,
resulting in both of them losing their dominant arm.
Naruto then gives one of his POWERFUL speeches,
AKA talk no jutsu, eliminating Sasuke's bad intension,
and so they do the rat hand sign,
releasing the infinite Tsuki No Me.
Returning to civilization, Kakashi is assigned hokage,
and Sasuke's in prison for the multiple
crimes he's accountable for.
Sasuke is then pardoned because of his contributions
stopping the infinite Tsuki No Me,
and also because Kakashi's the hokage.
With that said, Sasuke then leaves the Hidden Leaf,
to go on a journey to repent for his sins.
But before doing so, Naruto gives him a parting gift
on his way out, which is his old
Hidden Leaf edition, forehead protector.
And so as time goes by Naruto and Hinata get married and...
oh that's it.
*Weeb cover of Naruto Shippuden ED40*
(Belt whip)
Guy in the background: You really out here thinking I'm playing games.
Moe: But I was just singin—
(Belt whip) Guy in the background: SHUT YO ASS UP!
Alright, so thank you all for watching.
First and foremost I'd like to give a shout out to
James Brantley, Kirby Mars, and all my other
sexy ass Patreon supporters for
supporting this channel through Patreon.
It helps a ton when it comes to
these anime in minutes by the way.
So if you do support my anime in minutes,
by supporting me on Patreon that
actually helps a lot with the production
of these anime in minutes, allowing me to produce them
at a more frequent rate, because if you didn't know,
it takes a lot of god damn time.
But anyways, I did feel the need to remaster
my Naruto Shipudden in minutes because,
the audio quality was trash, and I feel like
the scripts could have been better.
And on top of that, I just had a lot of cringy ass parts,
simply because that was just an experiment video
believe or not, and it turned out to be my most viewed video
which is absolutely fucked.
But anyways once again thank you all for watching,
and I will see you guys next time.
Peace.